(Sheldon:)Or in layman's terms, string theory.
(Assistant:)I see.
(Assistant:)Just give me a second.
(Assistant:)Security!
(Raj:)Okay.
I'll get those drinks started for you.
(Sheldon(appearing in an apron and carrying a tray):)Behind you.
Sheldon? What the hell are you doing?
(Sheldon:)Trying to get these tables cleared.
We're slammed.
(Penny:)No, wait. Wait. No, wait.
What are you doing here?
(Sheldon:)A reasonable question.
I asked myself:
"What is the most mind-numbing,
pedestrian job conceivable?"
(Sheldon:)Three answers came to mind.
A toll booth attendant,
an Apple store genius...
(Sheldon:)...and what Penny does.
(Sheldon:)Now, since I don't like touching
other people's coins...
(Sheldon:)...and I refuse to contribute
to the devaluation of the word "genius"...